- What's your highest bounty?
- There is one job.
- Underworld?
- Deep pocket.
Greef Karga said you were
the best in the parsec.
I have a camtono of Beskar waiting
for you upon delivery of the asset.
You are Mandalorian!
I will help you.
Many have passed through.
They seek the same one.
IG Unit! Stand down.
You are a Guild member?
I have a suggestion. We split the reward.
This is acceptable.
The tracking fob is still active.
There is a life form present.
- Synced and corrected by VitoSilans -
... www.Addic7ed.com ...
I thought you were dead.
This is what was causing all the fuss?
I think it's a child.
It is better to deliver it alive then.
My ship has been destroyed.
I'm trapped here.
Stripped. Not destroyed.
The Jawas steal. They don't destroy.
Stolen or destroyed,
makes no difference to me.
They're protected by
their crawling fortress.
There's no way to recover the parts.
You can trade.
With Jawas? Are you out of your mind?
I will take you to them.
I have spoken.
Hey! Spit that out.
_
They really don't like
you for some reason.
Well, I did disintegrate a few of them.
You need to drop your rifle.
I'm a Mandalorian.
Weapons are part of my religion.
Then you are not
getting your parts back.
Fine.
And the blaster.
Good day.
They will trade all the
parts for the beskar.
I'm not gonna trade anything.
These are my parts.
They stole them from me.
_
- You understand this?
- No!
Whoa. Easy, easy.
_
Get away from it!
The egg? What egg?
_
Mando!
I have it.
I've got the egg.
I'm surprised you waited.
I'm surprised you took so long.
Is it still sleeping?
Yes.
Was it injured?
I don't think so. Not physically.
Explain it to me again.
I still don't understand what happened.
Neither do I.
There's no way we're
gonna get this to work
without a full maintenance facility.
This is gonna take days to fix.
If you care to help, it might go faster.
There is much work to do.
I can't thank you enough.
Please allow me to give
you a portion of the reward.
I cannot accept.
You are my guest and I am
therefore in your service.
I could use a crew member of your
ability, and I can pay handsomely.
I am honored,
but I have worked a lifetime
to finally be free of servitude.
I understand.
Then all I can offer is my thanks.
And I offer mine.
Thank you for bringing
peace to my valley.
And good luck with The Child.
May it survive and bring
you a handsome reward.
I have spoken.